[instrumental music]
[seagulls squawking]
[indistinct
police radio chatter]
Lovely.
Yeah. Used to be a fluorescent
light bulb factory.
Now it's a hazardous waste site.
There's mercury dust everywhere.
- Great.
- Yeah.
It's probably
not too dangerous
as long as you don't,
you know, breathe.
Some techs from the
hazardous materials office
came in to test the air.
Saw a lock on one of the
lockers, busted it open.
'That's when they found it.'
How long does the coroner think
he's been in there?
He said with that level
of decomp
at least six months.
Could be longer.
Handcuffs on the wrists,
ankles.
Did he have any clothes
or personal effects?
This. We found it
inside his ribcage.
[Lisbon]
'Probably something medical.'
Have the coroner's assistant
look at it.
Scratches on the doors.
Must be from his cuffs.
He was alive
when he was put inside.
How long would it take to die
in here? Like, five, six days?
That's the right place for it.
No one in earshot.
Make sure the techs search
every inch of this floor
and the one above.
[cell phone rings]
[sighs]
- What's up? Where are you?
- Yeah. Sorry, Lisbon.
I had my phone turned off.
We're in the middle
of a toxic waste dump. Hurry up.
Ooh. That sounds inviting.
I'll see you there.
'Chop chop.
Time's a-wastin'.'
[instrumental music]
[engine starts]
[birds chirping]
[music continues]
[Hailey]
'Hello, Patrick.'
Hello.
What's your name?
Hailey.
Well, it's nice to meet you,
How'd you know
my name was Patrick?
Your friend told me.
Which friend's that?
The one who brought me here.
He gave me this.
[intense music]
He didn't do anything else,
did he?
He told me to ask you
a question.
What's that?
He said to ask you..
...do you give up yet?
[music continues]
[instrumental music]
Apparently, Red John
or someone pretending to be him
lured the girl away from
a nearby park about an hour ago.
Her class was on a field trip.
It doesn't look like she was
harmed. Her mother's on her way.
Where's Jane?
Over there.
He hasn't said much.
Gonna run this note
they left for Jane
check it for prints andDNA.
You won't get any.
I know. It's worth a shot.
"Happy anniversary."
Today's the day that his wife
and daughter..
- I know. Nine years ago.
- Yeah.
- Would you excuse me, sir?
Hey there.
Hey there, yourself.
Hailey, this is, uh,
my friend Teresa.
- Hi, Hailey.
- I like your hair.
Thank you.
Patrick is teaching me
how to make a quarter disappear.
- The kid's a natural.
- No doubt.
Hailey, hello.
My name's Agent Wainwright.
Your mom's gonna
be here soon.
'When she gets here,
we're gonna talk to you'
'about the man you met.
Is that alright?'
What man?
The one who sent you
to Mr. Jane
who drew the face
on your hand.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Hailey, why don't you go
and show that policewoman
your new trick?
- Okay.
- Have fun.
Um, I...I don't understand.
She doesn't remember?
You hypnotized her.
No, I just planted a suggestion
for her to forget Red John.
Why would you do that?
She could identify him.
He's white.
He wore a baseball cap.
He had an odd voice.
Alright, look,
she might remember more
if she were
questioned properly.
Jane. Jane, she's a-a witness.
People who can identify Red John
end up dead.
I get that you feel
protective here.
Do you?
- This is not your call.
- Yes, it is.
If you try to question her
or even talk to her
I will hurt you badly.
Did he really
just threaten me?
Jane, I know it's hard coming
here, especially like this
and I'm sorry.
I'm not gonna ask you
to apologize
to Wainwright
but he's right.
The little girl's a witness.
We should interview her.
You know what Red John's
trying to do, don't you?
He asked me
if I'm ready to quit.
He's messing with your head.
Don't let him.
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm-I'm fine.
[cell phone ringing]
Appreciate your concern.
Your phone is ringing.
[ringing continues]
Hey, Rigsby.
So that thing that we found was
a surgical heart valve
implanted in the victim.
Traced the serial number on it
to a guy named Antonio Castro.
According to SFPD,
he disappeared 11 months ago.
[Lisbon]
Disappeared how?
He sent some e-mails from his
home on the night of June 17th.
'The next morning,
he was gone.'
'Car parked in the driveway.
Front door was locked.'
'No sign of forced entry
or struggle.'
His fiance filed a missing
persons report that afternoon.
SFPD find anything?
No. No contact with the family.
They're out of state.
No travel plans,
no enemies, no money troubles.
[Lisbon]
What'd he do for a living?
He's former military.
Two tours in Iraq.
'The past five years,
he's been working as a broker'
'in a financial company,
RF Victor.'
[Lisbon]
'Van Pelt, bring in
all the SFPD files'
and any physical evidence.
Cho, Rigsby,
I want you to put together
a time line and a list
of all the contacts
the victim had
before he disappeared.
We need to interview everybody.
Jane and I will go talk
to the people he worked with.
Jane.
Anything to offer?
Uh, well, there's not a lot
to go off, is there?
Your point being..
No point.
Shall we go?
Let's go.
Jane seem off to you?
Always.
[telephone ringing]
[indistinct chattering]
Oh. Dennis Victor.
Uh, you're from, uh, CBI?
Hi. I'm AgentLisbon,
and this is Patrick Jane.
You're absolutely positive
that you found Antonio's body?
Yes, sir. It was confirmed.
[sighs]
Well, we all knew
this day could come.
Still, a shock.
He was engaged to my niece.
I feel it very personally.
This way.
[Lisbon]
'What exactly do you
do here, Mr. Victor?'
[Victor]
'We're a financial derivatives
broker.'
'We offer
exchange-traded derivatives'
options, futures, and a few
over-the-counter products.
So basically,
you're just thieves
in, uh, ties and suspenders.
[laughs]
That would be
the popular view.
Not entirely accurate.
Up this way.
Agent Lisbon
Mr. Jane,
Ian Breitler.
He recruited
Antonio to the firm
'and he mentored him
during his first year.'
It's great to meet you.
Thanks for coming.
This is Ben Marx. He runs
the division Antonio was in.
He was his supervisor.
- Welcome.
- Sit. Please, sit.
[clears throat]
Mr. Jane.
Oh, I'm fine. Thank you.
What did Antonio Castro
do for you here?
He-he was a broker.
Handled customer accounts.
How'd he get along
with people?
Oh, he was universally loved,
a leader in the company.
[Ian]
'Absolutely.'
You don't agree?
Well, who's universally loved?
He was popular.
Do you know anything
about his family?
His mother's in a nursing home
in Flagstaff. Alzheimer's.
And his sister converted to
Islam and moved to Indonesia.
They weren't in touch.
And did he have
any problems at work?
Not that I was aware of.
No. All of his performance
reviews were exemplary.
Isn't that right, Ben?
If there were any issues
I wasn't aware of them
at the time.
- Mm. Interesting.
- Excuse me?
Well, he's telling the truth,
but you two aren't.
Something going on with Castro,
what was the big secret?
There wasn't one,
I assure you.
- Yes, there was.
- I'm afraid you're mistaken.
No, I'm-I'm sure,
just as I'm sure
you're not very fond
of Mr. Breitler here.
I'm Marx. He's Breitler.
Yes, well, whatever
your name is
your boss doesn't
like you very much
and I wouldn't be surprised
if he canned you very soon.
[Victor]
'That's a very interesting
observation because, uh'
Ben here was made a principal
in the firm last month
at my express request.
Okay.
- What's going on, Jane?
- Nothing.
Oh, I may be a little out of
sorts, but it's nothing serious.
Wanna get something to eat?
No, I think I might take
the rest of the day.
- You sure?
- Yeah, I'm gonna get a cab.
I'll see you tomorrow,
Lisbon.
Hello, Mr. Jane.
Good to see you again.
- You, too.
- Your table's ready.
Thank you.
And your order
will be right up.
Thank you.
[instrumental music]
[music continues]
[door rattles]
[sighs]
[dramatic music]
[Wainwright]
'Security tells me
the fire Jane started'
'could've burned down
the building.'
I know, sir.
I could suspend Jane
for this
but I think what happened
was a cry for help.
I just need to find out
what the issue is.
Me, too, sir.
If you don't mind, I think
I should do the talking.
Jane.
Mm.
[inhales deeply]
What's going on?
Well..
...I have a little hangover
uh, if you must know.
Why did you burn
your Red John files?
[exhales deeply]
Because he's right.
It's time to give up.
Seriously?
What do you mean?
Well, nothing's working.
Nothing.
It's just a game,
and he keeps winning.
The only way for me to stop him
is if I stop playing.
Meaning what?
Meaning I put it behind me.
I move on.
That's a big change, Jane.
[scoffs]
Well, change is good.
Isn't it?
So...are you
leaving the CBI?
No, of course not.
What would I do for amusement?
Speaking of which,
isn't there some person
or something we should be
investigating or such?
We're supposed to talk
to the victim's fiance.
Okay. Let's go.
Jane, I strongly recommend
that you talk to one of our
counselors about what happened.
I think it could help you.
Luther, there's no time.
I got perps to break.
Hey. How's the time line going?
Anything jump out?
Yeah. Castro did completely
normal stuff, then disappeared.
He was at a charity event,
right before he vanished, yeah?
What happened there?
It was a fund-raiser
for the homeless.
[sighs]
Witnesses say Castro was
calm, relaxed, left alone.
Are we gonna catch any
good breaks in this case?
I doubt it.
- What's the package?
- It's a baby monitor.
It's got audio and video.
Plus, it's 2-way,
so I can talk to Ben in his crib
without leaving my bed.
That should terrify him.
Hey. So I've been going through
the stuff SFPD collected
at Castro's office
and I found this, "19:24."
It was stuck
to a folder on his desk.
He was ex-military.
Could it be military time?
No, there wouldn't be a colon
between the nine and two.
It's something else.
Well, if you have any ideas,
let me know.
I'm not finding
anything else useful.
You know that Jane told Lisbon
he was giving up on Red John?
- Yeah.
- It's hard to believe.
You think he's losing it?
Like cracking up?
No.
- Nah.
Thank you for talking to us,
Miss Victor.
Of course. I would've met you
at the office but I jus..
I couldn't go in
after I heard the news.
How long were
you and Mr. Castro engaged?
Almost a year.
We'd been together
about two years before that.
And how did you meet?
Through work.
I'm with a PR agency
that handles financial firms,
including my uncle's.
Most of the guys that work in
finance are overgrown frat boys
but..
...Antonio was a man.
Maybe it was his time in the
service. I don't know but..
[exhales sharply]
...he was a great soul.
He was wise
and kind.
I'm sorry.
I thought
I was ready for this.
Did he have any enemies?
Antonio had a very strong sense
of morality.
He believed in
right and wrong
and would tell you
which was which.
I loved him for that,
but not everyone did.
Anyone in particular?
I can't think
of anyone offhand.
Uh, Lisbon, my head's a little
foggy and, uh, drifty
so I'm gonna push it
along a bit.
What are you guilty about?
I don't understand.
The tears and all the talk
of how wonderful he was.
He's been gone a year
and you're behaving like
he disappeared this morning.
- That's guilt.
- No, it's not.
It's not quite homicidal,
but there's something.
Were you cheating on him?
- No.
- Not while he was alive.
I bet now. Yes, that's it.
You've been sleeping around
on the sainted dead fiance.
- No, I haven't.
- Tell us the truth.
[sighs]
Well, it's complicated.
It's simple.
You've moved on. It happens.
You just don't want to admit it
because you think it looks bad.
Are you trying
to make me cry again?
No, I-I'm not.
I mean, I'm not
but if you want to, then..
...please, cry.
- Get it out.
- Jane.
Who is it, Marcy?
Hey, Cho, so Marcy Victor was
sleeping with Ian Breitler
which Breitler conveniently
forgot to tell us
when we talked to him.
Pick him up. See what
he has to say for himself.
Why did you hide your
relationship with Marcy Victor
Mr. Breitler?
Antonio was a sensitive topic
around the office, okay?
Until you guys found him
a lot of people were hoping
he'd come walking back
through the door.
Since you're sleeping
with his fiance
I'm guessing
you're not one of 'em.
I just didn't think
that the time to announce
that Marcy and I
are a couple
was when we had just found out
that Antonio was dead.
Hey, Cho.
Ian, what is that on your..
...jacket?
- There's...eh.
- What?
It's a hair.
That could be a clue.
It's my hair.
Hmm. Fair enough.
Ian doesn't think there's
anything significant
about his relationship
with Marcy Victor.
Yes, I'm inclined to agree.
Sleazy, maybe.
But motive for murder?
I don't think so.
I'm more interested
in Ian's other secret.
What's that?
The one that you
and Dennis Victor were keeping.
The one that has to do
with Antonio Castro's work.
Don't know what
you're talking about.
Oh.
You're tensing up, Ian.
And you have asthma.
That's not good.
That kind of tension goes
straight to the lungs
squeezes them, makes them
get smaller and smaller.
Is there a question here?
The windpipe shrinks up
and every breath you take
is harder than the last.
It's hard to breathe.
The last thing you
want to do is get upset.
- This is ridiculous.
- Don't panic.
What are you looking for?
What is it? Is it this?
Gimme that.
Tell me what I need to know.
[sighs]
You can't do that.
- He can't-he can't do that.
- He's doing it.
[sighs]
Yeah, you know,
you're probably right.
- Changed my mind.
- For God sake.
[sighs]
I'm calling my lawyer.
Sure. Go ahead. It'll only take
him an hour to get here.
[exhales deeply]
[groans]
Castro was a thief.
He was stealing
from the firm.
We didn't find out
until after he disappeared
when Marx took over
his accounts.
Mm.
Hey!
Come on!
[exhales deeply]
- How much did Castro steal?
- Breitler says he doesn't know.
Marx and Dennis Victor
didn't share
the numbers
with anyone else.
Why didn't they tell us that
to start with?
Victor's order. No one
was allowed to say anything.
Alright, let's bring him in
and sort it out.
- Sure.
- Hey.
How does Jane seem to you?
Different.
I think he's in trouble.
Me, too. Where is he?
He said he still had a headache.
Went out to go get some Aspirin.
Alright.
[birds chirping]
Mr. Wineman.
Beautiful cemetery.
You should be proud.
So neat.
Mm. Thank you. Uh, what-what
can I do for you, Mr. Jane?
Well, like I said on the phone,
um, I'm with the CBI.
We're pursuing
a particularly vicious killer.
Tough case.
But with your help,
we can crack it.
You're not using this grave
right away, are you?
No. The services aren't until
the day after tomorrow.
Good.
We'll be done by then.
Wh-what do you mean done?
We need to run
a small police operation here.
Nothing I can tell you about,
but you can help us.
Help us remove a very dangerous
killer from the street.
You want to help us,
don't you?
You'll help us?
- Help? Uh, y-yes. Of course.
- Good.
We'll need a coffin as well.
Nothing too fancy.
- A coffin?
- Yes. Down there.
After Antonio vanished,
Ben here took over his accounts
and four weeks in,
he found something.
Antonio was stealing money
from customers
and hiding it with paper losses
on fictional investments.
He'd been doing it
for about six months.
- 'Mm.'
- How much money did he steal?
Oh, we'll never be sure.
Somewhere between
seven and ten million.
- Where's the money?
- We have no idea.
Antonio's transactions were
brilliantly complex.
The money's
essentially untraceable.
[Cho]
'This wasn't
in the SFPD files.'
- 'Did you tell them?'
- 'No, they didn't ask.'
And we didn't discover
the theft
until after
they had interviewed us.
You could've picked up
the phone.
Agent, because we discovered
the theft internally
we were able to make good
on our customers' losses.
They don't even know
they were robbed.
That cost my firm
a great deal of money
but it saved us
major embarrassment.
And I couldn't see any value
in publicizing
what had been
so fortunately hidden.
It was evidence
in a homicide.
Well, we had to balance justice
with self-preservation.
[Marx]
'Absolutely.'
I think we found
a very good middle course.
This is obstruction of justice,
and I'm gonna have you charged.
I'm sorry. You-you asked
if we knew about anything
Antonio had done at the time.
Right? We said we didn't know
anything at the time.
- Mm.
- All true.
- Tell it to your lawyers.
- No need.
We are lawyers.
If there's nothing else..
[clears throat]
- Jane.
- What?
I'm trying to figure out
what this number
on Castro's desk means.
The only thing I can find are
a couple of references
to some sort
of high-end social club.
Any idea why they'd name it
19:24?
The Bible.
Matthew 19:24.
"Again I say unto you,
it is easier for a camel
to go through the eye
of a needle than it is"--
"Than for a rich man to enter
the kingdom of heaven."
- Yes.
- That's weird.
Well, it's an ironic joke.
Since the rich
won't get into heaven
they should enjoy
their life on earth.
Okay, but why did Castro care?
He wasn't a member,
far as I can tell.
Mm. Of course he wasn't.
Well, that clears things up.
[elevator bell dings]
Oh, guys!
[clears throat]
Tell me about, uh, 19:24.
And don't deny
you're members
'cause I can see it
all over your faces.
Well, you know,
it's-it's a club.
Small, private.
For the filthy rich?
- For people of means.
- Oh.
No one is supposed
to talk about it.
First rule of fight club
and all that.
Okay.
Who else is members?
- Breitler? Your niece?
- Both of them.
Lots of people from my firm,
other firms.
So i-if your niece
was a member
then surely, uh, Antonio Castro
was asked about joining.
- 'Yes.'
- Yeah.
Shortly before
he disappeared.
Right. And to become a member
of this, um, fancy
elite little club, uh
I'm assuming you need to
have some kind of a hazing.
[chuckles]
Yes.
Prospective members are tapped
by current members
and forced to do all sorts
of embarrassing things.
[laughs]
Oh.
- Good fun.
- Sure.
This charity event
that Antonio Castro attended
the night he disappeared,
was that held at the club?
As a matter of fact, it was.
Antonio was there as a guest.
[elevator bell dings]
Mm.
You interested in membership,
Mr. Jane?
- Me?
- Yeah.
Uh, no. No.
Not the club type.
- Oh.
- Thank you.
I've got an accountant
looking at Castro's trades
but they're so complicated, he
can barely make sense of them.
What else do we have?
I talked to 13 people
who met with Castro
before he disappeared.
Nothing unusual or suspicious.
I've been through
all the forensic evidence
SFPD gathered from Castro's
apartment and office.
- Nothing jumps out.
- Time line?
- 'Nothing that leads anywhere.'
- 'We don't have anything.'
We have something. We just
don't know what it is yet.
I do. Let's go.
- Where?
- Uh, 19:24 club.
I convinced Marcy Victor
to throw an emergency meeting.
- What for?
- To solve the case, of course.
Where'd you get this?
[indistinct chattering]
[Jane]
'Do you have
the exits covered?'
Rigsby, Cho, and Van Pelt
are by the doors.
Okay.
Hello, everybody.
Thank you for coming.
I'm Patrick Jane with the CBI.
As you've been told,
we're investigating the death
of Marcy Victor's fiance
Antonio Castro.
What you haven't been told is
that the killer is in this room.
All I need to identify him
are the answers
to a few questions.
- What kind of questions?
- Very simple ones.
Uh, you, ma'am,
the frayed thread on your sleeve
'plus last season's shoes
suggest money trouble. True?'
No. No, I've..
No, we're fine.
[chuckles]
Uh, we're fine.
See? A lie.
Did you kill Antonio Castro?
I didn't even know him.
And there's the truth.
When I watch you tell a lie
it helps me determine whether
you're telling the truth.
For example, Marcy here
is sleeping with Ian.
You're not committed to him
emotionally, and you don't think
he's half the man that
your fiance was, do you?
No, that's not true.
A lie.
Thank you very much.
- Did you kill Antonio?
- Of course not.
And there's the truth.
- Is this some kind of joke?
- Please be patient.
Take a seat, ma'am.
Mr. Marx, you're more
than a little twisted
'in the bedroom,
aren't you?'
'Latex and whips are your thing,
are they not?'
[indistinct murmur]
Not at all.
Did you kill Antonio Castro?
No, I did not.
Hmm. Uh, you, sir.
[chuckles]
If you think
I'm saying a word
without a lawyer on either side
of me, you're crazy.
And any of you that put up with
this is as crazy as he is.
Ladies and gentlemen.
If everybody could just stay
in the room, please.
[indistinct chattering]
I don't understand.
What were you trying to do?
The plan was to, uh
scare the killer
into making a run for it.
You thought that would work?
Certainly had a fair chance,
I thought.
I'm gonna go tell Rigsby
and the others to stand down.
You stay here.
Yeah, it was crazy. I'll tell
you about it when I get there.
Alright. Bye.
- Marx!
- Mr. Jane.
That didn't work out for you
so well, did it?
No, it went pretty much
as planned.
- The case is cracked.
- Oh, yeah?
- Is that your car?
- Yep.
- Wow. That's a nice ride.
- Thanks.
Let's take a little drive.
I'll tell you all about it.
- Ride where?
- Oh, not far.
I mean, don't you want to be
the first to know who did it?
Okay.
- What's in the bag?
- Oh, a baby monitor.
[chuckles]
I-I'll explain later.
Turn right up here.
So how exactly did that mess
back at the club
work out for you,
Mr. Jane?
Wasn't looking for a killer.
I was looking for a liar.
Someone that can answer
an embarrassing question
in public
without getting flustered.
Hmm.
Why was that important?
Castro's killer was
a vicious sadist.
Someone that truly enjoyed
watching other people's pain.
He can't show it.
Ergo, a first-rate liar.
And you found him?
Sure.
It was you.
Turn, uh, here.
Me?
I noticed when we first talked,
you and, uh, Victor and Breitler
said that Castro hadn't done
anything wrong
and I could tell
the other two were lying
but you seemed
to be telling the truth.
And not too many people
fool me like that.
So I tested you again
at the club.
- Oh, yeah?
- Mm.
- How'd I do?
- Outstanding.
One of the best liars
I've ever seen.
It explains your success
in sales
and, uh,
the kinky sex life.
Just, uh, just-just pull in
a little up here.
None of that means
I killed Antonio.
Sure, it does.
- I can prove it.
- How?
Walk with me,
and I'll show you.
[intense music]
Castro didn't take the money.
Too much of a boy scout.
It was you that stole it.
Castro had figured out
that someone was stealing
so he, uh,
he came to you.
Why?
Because you're his boss.
What he didn't realize,
that you were also the thief.
Something's wrong
with the future tallies.
I-I just can't
put my finger on what.
Alright.
Okay. I'll look into it.
[Jane]
Then you had to kill him.
How exactly did I do that?
Kind of brilliantly,
I have to say.
[Jane]
The 19:24 club
was the ticket.
Castro was gonna join, and the night the charity function
took place, you told him
he was gonna be initiated
but he had to be hazed first.
- You ready?
- Now?
Shh. It's supposed to be
a surprise.
Get your car
and meet me around the corner.
I'm gonna drive you there.
But don't tell anybody
where you're going
or what you're doing, okay?
Exactly how embarrassing
is this gonna be?
Awesomely, my brother.
But I do have a
little help here for you.
Make it go a lot easier.
Trust me.
So you took him
to the factory.
You walked him downstairs..
...to the basement.
He did everything you asked.
What the hell?
Yeah. Be careful..
- Yeah.
- It'll be alright.
Drawers too.
- In the box.
- Get in the box.
You can do it.
Alright, Antonio,
you good?
- Yeah. What now?
- Just you wait.
[door hinges creaks]
And then you went
to his house
and sent e-mails
from his computer
so that no one could connect
his disappearance
with the club or you.
Mm. Well, this-that sounds
pretty cool.
Except Castro was a thief.
All the trades were
on his account.
You had weeks
to fake that data.
I bet that wasn't
very hard for you.
Ooh. Gosh, I must be
a very bad man.
Vicious and heartless.
You gave Castro the most
terrifying death possible.
You're evil.
Where's your proof?
- You're gonna confess to me.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
- Why would I do that?
What, you're gonna scare me
into saying that I did it?
That's your plan?
Yeah, that's the plan.
[dramatic music]
[birds chirping]
Hey.
Good morning,Lisbon.
'Got your message.'
What are you doing here?
Resting.
Solved the case.
Really?
Yeah, it was Benjamin Marx.
He stole the money,
killed Castro
and pinned
the theft on him.
- How do you know that?
- He's gonna confess.
- Gonna confess?
- Mm. Very soon, I think.
Where is he?
Uh..
...he's here.
[Jane]
'Oh. Sorry.'
[grunts]
Somebody help me!
Jane, help me! Please!
Yeah, he-he does go on.
Y-you locked him
in a coffin?
Yeah. Give him a taste
of his own medicine.
Where is he?
How long has he been in there?
We have to get him out.
He'll die.
- Not until he confesses.
- Jane, you can't do this.
Sure, I can.
Watch this.
- Marx, you hear me?
- Jane! Jane, help, me, please.
Please! I can't breathe!
No problem. Just admit
to killing Castro.
[grunts]
- Marx.
- No!
Okay. Die.
Jane, tell me where he is.
I mean it.
- Marx, you change your mind?
- Jane.
Oh, God! Oh! Oh! Oh!
Jane!
Okay, I'm gonna walk away
from here
and no one
will ever find you.
Yes! Yes! Yes!
I did it!
Yeah, I-I killed Antonio.
'You locked him in that box.'
- 'And you left him to die.'
- I did. I did. I did.
Please. Get me out of here.
You must have kept a trophy.
Where is it?
Yes! Okay. Okay. Okay.
His key ring. His key ring.
There's an army insignia on it.
In a box, okay? Top shelf,
bedroom closet. Okay? Please.
Well, there you go.
He's, uh, over by that tree.
I need an ambulance
at the Willow Wood Cemetery
as soon as possible.
God, Jane!
[indistinct police radio
chatter]
What'd you find?
Okay.
[Lisbon]
'Cho said
they found the key ring'
'in the exact place
Marx said it would be.'
'Let's go see Wainwright.'
'Come on.'
You know, I really
can't see the problem.
I closed the case.
You solved what-what case?
There is no case.
No judge is ever gonna let
that confession stand.
They're gonna throw out
the key chain also.
Marx is
never gonna see a trial.
Meh. Let the lawyers
sort it out.
Cho and the accountants
have already found evidence
in Castro's
trading accounts
that it was Marx
who stole the money.
'The DA is gonna charge him
with theft and security fraud.'
Now I think we can build
a murder case
on top of that
without the confession.
- See?
- I don't care.
You assaulted Marx.
Sac PD wants to arrest you.
Marx had a gun.
That's self-defense.
I think a jury
will believe me.
Jane is under a tremendous
amount of stress.
I'm fine, thank you.
Look, you tortured the guy,
for Christ sakes.
Jane, you tortured him.
Do you have any notion
how that makes the CBI look?
I gave an evil psychopath
justice.
Now does anyone here think that
Marx didn't deserve what he got?
I think he deserved it.
Thank you, Grace.
Anyone else?
Cho? Rigsby?
- No, I get it. It's okay.
- Jane, you crossed the line.
Yes, of course I did.
I crossed the line.
I had to to get Marx. It was
the only way to get Marx.
If you don't get the bad guy,
then what's the point
of all this?
I'm not gonna apologize.
Maybe you should take
a time-out.
You know what?
That's a good idea.
You're suspended
as of this moment.
You're not gonna come
into this office.
You're not gonna have
anything to do with the CBI.
There'll be a hearing
on your status in 30 days.
And I want you to know
I'm gonna personally recommend
CBI discontinue you permanently
as a consultant.
I understand that you're under
some distress, Jane
but youshamed us today.
And I'm not gonna
let that happen again.
You're a pathetic little boy.
- Excuse me?
- You're a child.
Daddy was mean to you.
He thought you were soft.
You're a mama's boy.
I'm s..
This has--
Oh, go home, little boy.
Go home to mama.
'Go on. Off to mama.'
- Jane, stop.
- Oh, come on.
'He's a pathetic, little,
mewling mama's boy.'
He's still got her milk
on his lip. Look at him. Huh?
[chuckles]
- Hey! Hey!
- Whoa, boss!
[Cho]
Take it easy.
Come on. I'm gonna kill you.
- 'Boss.'
- Get off me.
[indistinct chattering]
- Come on!
- Okay. Okay. Get off of me.
Get off of me.
[intense music]
On second thought,
you're not suspended.
You're fired.
Get out of here right now.
[instrumental music]
Jane.
Jane, don't do anything rash.
We can work this out.
We'll fix it.
I doubt that.
I'll come by your place tonight.
We'll talk it out, okay?
You're sweet.
Let me help you.
[elevator bell dings]
[elevator whirring]
[theme music]